<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Unofficial CPSSD Homepage</title>
    <link>https://cpssd.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Unofficial CPSSD Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ie</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cpssd.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CPSSD Research Project Published In ACL 2019 Conference</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/lucas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/lucas/</guid>
      <description>Taking the latest and greatest advances in natural language processing and deep learning, CPSSD students trained a series of models to classify human deception in datasets of user submitted reviews. The output of the research was threefold: a scientific paper describing our research; an open source API providing access to query our trained models; and Lucify, a web interface allowing end users to view an interactive and comprehensive report of review deception and legitimacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: Dipla</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/dipla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/dipla/</guid>
      <description>Dipla is a distributed computing framework for Python built by Cian Ruane, Noah Donnelly, Brandon Ibbotson and Stefan Kennedy.
Goals Our original goal and the main guiding principle behind Dipla was to build a framework that was easy to reason about from the outside but still quite clever on the inside. Our hope was that we could create something that allowed people to write distributed Python code that looked almost the same as if it were running locally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students in CPSSD Provide 72% of Ireland&#39;s Total Score on Kattis</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/blog/2017-kattis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/blog/2017-kattis/</guid>
      <description>Kattis is an online judge for competitive programming problems, that some CPSSD students have been using to practise for various competitions. You can read about our success at 2017&amp;rsquo;s HashCode, for example.
The website includes a list of problems, of varying degrees of difficulty. When a user solves a problem, they get between 1 and 10 points based on how hard that problem is; the harder the problem, the higher the points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPSSD Taking No New Entries</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/blog/rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/blog/rip/</guid>
      <description>Tá CPSSD marbh, go maire &amp;lt;TBD&amp;gt;.
On the 17th of November, all the current students of CPSSD (née PSSD) receieved an email from Rory O&amp;rsquo;Connor, the Head of the School of Computing in DCU, detailing the suspension of the course. Unfortunately, the email had the bog-standard TOS at the bottom of all university emails warning me not to share it here (curse non-free-as-in-speech licences).
It described that:
 There will be no first year CPSSD group in 2017&amp;frasl;2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPSSD Tackles Hashcode 2017</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/blog/2017-hashcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/blog/2017-hashcode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://hashcode.withgoogle.com&#34;&gt;Hashcode&lt;/a&gt; qualification round took
place on the 23rd of February, and lots of CPSSD first and second years crowded
in the DCU Hashcode hub to compete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Year Experiences</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/blog/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/blog/tips/</guid>
      <description>Around New Year&amp;rsquo;s, I wrote a wee article on what I&amp;rsquo;d experienced over the first semester of CPSSD. It might be a useful read for someone to see what the course content is like in that first semester, or for someone who is about to start the course and has to decide on their modules.
However, more recently, Cian Ruane wrote a post where he broke down the structure of the course across the whole year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: Feedlark</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/feedlark/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/feedlark/</guid>
      <description>Feedlark is an RSS aggregator built by Aaron Delaney, Lucas Savva, Cian Ruane, Ross O&amp;rsquo;sullivan and Noah Donnelly.
Feedlark aims to be efficient, fast, and smart. Users can get updates on RSS or Atom feeds they follow through a slick Material Design interface. They can receive email summaries of their stream, view their stream through a plaintext endpoint (ideal for command line usage!) and bookmark articles for later.
What&amp;rsquo;s more, a user can upvote and downvote articles according to their interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: kRAYate</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/krayate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/krayate/</guid>
      <description>Krayate is a simple game engine that uses raycast rendering.
It seeks to evoke the feeling of early 3d rendered games such as DOOM and Wolfenstein 3D. Krayate features a custom programming language, and allows users to design interactable objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/about/</guid>
      <description>About CPSSD Computational Problem Solving and Software Development (CPSSD) is an undergraduate computing course in Dublin City University that requires applicants to have prior knowledge of programming. This means that students can save time re-learning the basisc, and jump straight into making some Cool Things.
The course had a special admission procedure, Applicants do not need to worry about points, but must submit a portfolio, pass an interview, achieve the minimum DCU requirements, and pass honours maths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/students/</guid>
      <description>Current List of Students Here is a list of all the students of CPSSD.
If anyone is missing, you can submit a pull request on Github. There&amp;rsquo;s no nned to link anyone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the links to seal the deal.
If you have any questions about the course, you can probably find someone here to spam.
There is a partial Twitter list of CPSSD-related accounts. Ping [Noah] if you want to be added.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>