<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on The Unofficial CPSSD Homepage</title>
    <link>https://cpssd.net/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on The Unofficial CPSSD Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ie</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cpssd.net/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: Dipla</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/dipla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/dipla/</guid>
      <description>Dipla is a distributed computing framework for Python built by Cian Ruane, Noah Donnelly, Brandon Ibbotson and Stefan Kennedy.
Goals Our original goal and the main guiding principle behind Dipla was to build a framework that was easy to reason about from the outside but still quite clever on the inside. Our hope was that we could create something that allowed people to write distributed Python code that looked almost the same as if it were running locally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: Feedlark</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/feedlark/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/feedlark/</guid>
      <description>Feedlark is an RSS aggregator built by Aaron Delaney, Lucas Savva, Cian Ruane, Ross O&amp;rsquo;sullivan and Noah Donnelly.
Feedlark aims to be efficient, fast, and smart. Users can get updates on RSS or Atom feeds they follow through a slick Material Design interface. They can receive email summaries of their stream, view their stream through a plaintext endpoint (ideal for command line usage!) and bookmark articles for later.
What&amp;rsquo;s more, a user can upvote and downvote articles according to their interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: kRAYate</title>
      <link>https://cpssd.net/project/krayate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpssd.net/project/krayate/</guid>
      <description>Krayate is a simple game engine that uses raycast rendering.
It seeks to evoke the feeling of early 3d rendered games such as DOOM and Wolfenstein 3D. Krayate features a custom programming language, and allows users to design interactable objects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>